[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
♪ Even though my heart says I love you ♪
♪ Why am I like this? ♪
♪ I don't understand ♪
♪ What's wrong with my mouth and my heart? ♪
♪ Why won't they say the same thing? ♪
♪ Will we ever get to love each other? ♪
I found a new potential investor who doesn't seem difficult to deal with.
I'm so happy for you.
You mean Parn isn't coming back to work?
She won't accept me as a client anymore?
Can you promise me something, Parn?
Promise me that you won't lie.
Then give me back my money.
I'm trying to get it.
But I really don't have it right now.
Sis!
I'll hurry and get the money to pay you back.
One week.
You must return the whole amount.
Can you borrow Ms. Peem?
I don't think we should.
Come on, she has hundreds of millions. Borrowing ten won't make a dent in her fortune.
Sis, but people will start thinking I'm after her money right away.
But if we can't find it in seven days,
the two of us are surely dead.
Do your best in class, okay?
Okay.
Is something wrong?
No.
You should go to work, Peem.
You didn't tell Ms. Peem?
I'm worried here because I didn't tell her.
Why didn't you tell her?
Will she understand?
She thinks what I do is selling my body.
If I told her and she didn't allow me to come, what would Sis do?
She got in debt herself but expects you to help pay for it.
That's already wrong of her.
Ah-ah-ah!
Gratitude is one thing.
But if you have to break up with Ms. Peem because of this,
she won't be able to take responsibility, you know.
This is our new shopping mall.
I think this new project could help expand both our business models.
If you’d like to see our malls, I can show you around.
Before I came here to see you,
I had visited every one of your malls.
Right now, I’d much rather have a meal with you.
Why did you ask to have a meal with me?
I'd like to get to know you better.
I want to know what you’re like when you’re not working.
Am I being too direct?
I'm not that interesting.
You are interesting.
Even I am interested.
♪ Turn that body up ♪
Hey.
If you sit with the clients for me at a few tables,
you can make ten million in no time.
We've talked about this.
I'm not accepting any clients and I'm not drinking.
I'm only here to bring in clients and entertain them.
I'm not selling my time to anyone anymore.
Sure, lover girl.
I know you give all your 24 hours to Ms. Peem.
That's right.
I'm already grateful that you came to help me bring in more clients
By the way, won't she wonder why you're going home at 9 p.m. like this?
She's been working hard lately.
She comes home late every day
because an investor from Singapore is here.
Oh, so that's why you're only working here for seven days.
Yeah.
After seven days, I guess I won't be coming here anymore.
I don't want to lie to her.
That's good.
I don't want you to do this job even for a day.
I want you live like a madam, comfortably, and happily.
And stay rich until you're old, so you can treat us to meals at expensive restaurants.
You come home quite late, huh?
I was at the bakery. And I was trying to come up with recipes for what I want to sell.
I've been busy lately. I haven't really had much time for you.
It's okay.
There's nothing I need your help with right now.
But if I need your help and you won't come,
you're gonna get it.
I want it now.
Quit it.
Go take a shower.
You've been learning and baking since morning. It must be a long day.
Well.
I'll go take a shower then.
If you don't stop now...
I've stopped.
Can I join you?
Thought you wouldn't ask.
♪ Feels like we're fading out ♪
♪ I'm losing you ♪
♪ Can't we try again? ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ Feels like we're fading out ♪
♪ I'm losing you ♪
♪ Oh, can't we try again? ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ Baby, we can work it out ♪
♪ Maybe you can stay the night ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ I don't wanna let you go ♪
♪ I just wanna let you know ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ Baby, we can work it out ♪
♪ Maybe you can stay the night ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ Don't let this go to waste ♪
♪ I don't wanna let you go ♪
♪ I just wanna let you know ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ Hope that we can work it out ♪
♪ Wanna feel you close to me ♪
♪ I hope that we can work it out ♪
I'm off to work now.
I made breakfast for you. It's on the table.
Okay.
Do your best in class and come home soon, okay?
I don't think I can accept the job anymore.
Didn't you say it's a separate matter?
I just feel uncomfortable doing this to Ms. Peem.
Please, Parn.
This time, it's really necessary.
I beg you.
Fine, but this is the last time, okay?
You basically disappeared.
Oops.
Then, please excuse me.
Next time we meet, I think we can talk about the numbers.
- Sure. - I'll take my leave, then.
Goodbye.
So this is why you disappeared.
You didn't answer when I asked you to play tennis.
And you ignored me when I said we should grab a bite.
All this time, you were busy with this guy.
He's gorgeous.
He's a Singaporean investor who's going to invest with us, so I'm busy.
Yeah, I saw the news.
It's all over my feed.
You don't need to tell me. They already told me everything.
There are even photos of you guys walking in the malls and eating together.
Oh, they captured everything you did.
Hey, come back and tell me everything. What happened?
Hey, hey.
So what's going on?
- Not what you think. - Ah!
No "ah."
I came all the way here because I thought you got yourself a boyfriend.
I wanted to tease you.
You disappeared, so I thought you're head over heels in love and forgot about your friend.
Turns out, you're still single.
Jeez.
I was hoping he could introduce me to his friends.
What a bummer.
I already have someone.
Huh?!
You have someone?
Yeah, I do.
I want you two to meet.
But I've been busy lately, so I don't have time.
You can't do that.
I'm free, so set it up.
Even if you ask when I'm busy, I'll make myself free. I want to meet them.
I want to see the face of the person Peem loves.
How about this?
Let's meet up this evening.
Go reschedule things with your secretary, and bring them to see me at the restaurant.
I think I need to touch up my makeup a bit.
She's not answering.
Excuse me. Where's Parn?
Ms. Parn didn't come today.
She called in this morning.
What time, baby?
Oh.
Jeez.
Oh, finally, baby, come on.
Why are you here alone?
You said you're bringing her.
- Hm? - She wasn't there.
Why don't you call her?
I did. She didn't answer.
Huh? What the heck?
Hey, it's fine. Don't worry. We can meet later.
Let's look at this instead.
The gossip of the day.
I'm sure you'll like it.
A friend of mine ran into him at the hotel today.
He's with a woman, a pretty one too.
We're all floored
We've been saying he's gay for ages.
Look now.
Peem.
Look.
Here.
Hey. Hey.
Look here a bit. Pay a little attention to me, okay?
Look a bit.
He's actually your business rival, you know.
I had someone follow him for quite a while before I got this photo.
You have to give me credit for being so clever.
Hey, Peem.
Peem.
I'm not eating anymore. My stomach hurts. I want to go home.
Hey. Peem.
Peem.
What's wrong with her?
Stomach hurts? Going home?
Just say it if you wanna ditch me.
Where have you been?
A baking class, of course.
And I stop by the shop every day to practice.
Aw.
You missed me?
I'll take a shower quickly and then let's cuddle.
Keep me updated at all times. Understand?
Yes.
Is this your last day?
Well, you've already got your ten million.
You don't think I should save some for later too?
Ms. Peem has been coming home early for two days now.
I'm afraid I might get caught.
But you didn't do anything wrong, Parn.
You don't drink. You don't make drinks for them. You don't sit and talk with them.
You're just walking around greeting the guests. Can't she understand that?
Today's going to be my last day, Sis.
I'll go along with whatever you say.
Peem.
Don't call my name with your filthy mouth.
Don't be mad.
Do you like being a whore that much?
Is that why you lied to me?
Peem.
If there's anything else you want, just let me know.
You're regulars. Please feel free.
Sis!
Sorry. Hey.
Sis, we're doomed.
What?
Ms. Peem is yelling at Parn in the front.
Peem.
Let go.
Don't call my name.
Will you please hear me out?
About what?
The lie you made up to fool a fool like me?
Why should I do that?
I know I was wrong.
What did you do wrong?
Going to the hotel with Techin?
Lying to me?
Or coming back here to work?
You deceived me.
You think I'm stupid?
I didn't mean to deceive you.
I'm just helping her out temporarily.
She really has no money.
And about Mr. Techin,
it's not what you think.
Right. It's really not what I think.
I thought you stopped getting involved with him when you started seeing me.
But you didn't stop.
You never stopped.
Ms. Peem.
Pack your things and get out of my house.
Get out of my life.
I don't want to see you again.
Parn!
Parn.
Sit down. I'll put this away for you.
Sit.
Do you want me to go tell her you're helping me pay off my debt?
I think that's a good idea. She'll probably listen to her.
I don't think you should
Then what are you going to do?
If you go back to apologize,
will she even listen to you?
I don't know.
I'll go home and talk to her, Sis.
Ms. Peem.
Can you promise me something, Parn?
Promise me that you won't lie.
I don't know how long this happiness will last.
It'll be long.
It could even last a lifetime.
She lied about everything.
Was there nothing real between us?
Ms. Peem.
♪ Even though my heart says I love you ♪
♪ Why am I like this... ♪
Is it good?
♪ I don't understand ♪
♪ What's wrong with my mouth and my heart? ♪
♪ Why... ♪
You told me that just staying by your side is enough.
So I want to be by your side
when you have to face things like this.
♪ Just the one word, love ♪
♪ I don't understand why I can't say it ♪
♪ Why do I keep it to myself? ♪
♪ I can only be angry with myself For acting so cold ♪
♪ Making something so simple so complicated ♪
♪ Even though my heart says... ♪
I don't want you to think that I was with you for the money.
All this time, I truly loved you.
♪ I don't understand ♪
♪ What's wrong with my mouth and my heart? ♪
♪ Why won't they say the same thing? ♪
♪ Will we ever get to love each other? ♪
She probably doesn't want me to live there anymore.
Now that you've left, when will you two get to talk again?
I don't think we'll ever talk again.
I think it's over.
Have you told her about Mr. Techin?
I beg you, Parn.
What do I have to do?
Just go see my family.
You've done it several times.
My family thinks we're dating now.
You can't just suddenly disappear.
At least,
this time, we can pretend to fight.
When I go to see them next time, I can tell them we've broken up.
Why don't you just tell them?
I'm an only son, Parn.
What do you think they'll think...
if they know I'm gay?
How could I reveal his secret?
Plus, they know each other.
Jeez! If I were you, I'd tell her.
I'd tell her everything.
Are you crazy?
If you tell her and it ruins him, that's his problem.
But if you're not telling her, it's going to ruin you, you know?
This is 100% your problem.
I can still hear the phone buzzing.
There she is! Is she dead?
What am I supposed to hear?
Heartbeat, sir.
Heartbeat, right.
Oh, it twitched!
Oh my!
How long has she been dead?
Is the body already stiff?
Not yet.
Not stiff yet.
Not dead.
Right, her leg can still move, so she's probably alive.
Peem!
Jeez!
Get up if you're not dead.
Jeez! You scared me!
Thank you.
No problem at all. If you need help with anything, please feel free to call me.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I thought you'd shriveled up and died here in your condo.
That's why I rushed here.
Thanks for your concern.
Well, and that person...
- Gone. - Huh?
Gone?
You want her to stay to rub it in my face that I'm a fool?
Are you a fool?
In the current situation, yes.
Is it that bad?
Are you okay?
She changed my mind about women like my mom.
I used to think these sex workers are always after money.
But she convinced me that I was wrong.
But right now,
I don't know what's real and what's not.
And I don't understand why she did this to me.
And I've fallen in love with her.
I love her more than anything else in my life.
It's okay. I'm here.
I'm here with you.
You have me.
I'd like to see Ms. Peem.
Ms. Peem isn't coming in today.
Do you happen to know when she'll come in again?
We're not informed about that at all.
I recommend calling her secretary to schedule your meeting first.
Okay.
Here, get up and swing it, girl.
Let it all out, come on.
Hey.
Here.
You two can break up, but you can't go around acting soulless like this. Get up!
Jeez.
Just be like the day you failed to close the deal.
You two couldn't make it work because your needs didn't align.
When you can't reach an agreement, you just break up and go your separate ways.
Okay?
It's as simple as that.
Why would you date a bad person, huh?
- Hey! - Ouch!
Did it hurt?
- Of course, it hurt. - If it hurt, then move.
Be a little bit more lively.
Come on.
- I want to play now. - Ugh.
You can do it!
The Peem that I know is chic, fabulous, and smart.
She doesn't care about anyone.
Go back to being your old self.
Let her see that she doesn't have that much power over you.
Ms. Peem, here are the documents you need to sign.
Also, Mr. David wants to schedule a meeting to discuss the price after this.
Would you like to accept the invitation?
Go ahead.
Also...
What else?
Ms. Parn came to see you every day.
She came today too.
Would you like to see her, Ms. Peem?
Okay.
Let her wait in the reception room.
Ms. Peem asked you to wait in this room.
Thank you.
- Mr. Techin didn't want me to... - I don't want an explanation.
Was your life so hard when you're with me?
Why did you have to accept the job again?
- Sis Mol needs money to... - I asked if you didn't have enough money.
Was your life so hard that you had to accept the job again?
If it's so hard to be mine alone,
just go back to being Paradise's Angel.
And don't show me your face again.
I don't want to see the face of a whore like you.
♪ Even though my heart says I love you ♪
♪ Why am I like this? ♪
♪ I don't understand ♪
♪ What's wrong with my mouth and my heart? ♪
♪ Why won't they say the same thing? ♪
♪ Will we ever get to love each other? ♪
♪ Just the one word, love ♪
♪ I don't understand why I can't say it ♪
♪ Why do I keep it to myself? ♪
Mmm! What a surprise, baby!
Good job! You did the right thing. That's my girl.
Why do you keep sighing?
You did the right thing, Peem.
Let her know that someone like you is rare to find.
Hey, don't be sad.
Make her realize that, for someone like you,
if she messes up, even if she comes crawling back to beg at your feet,
she will never get you back.
Haha!
You have us here, you know.
That's right. You still have me.
Oh, and what about your shop?
The rent, the decoration, and all the other expenses you have to cover.
That's not a small amount of money.
I'll work.
If so,
do you want to come back and work for me temporarily?
Until your shop is finished.
The decoration will cost quite a lot.
If you just have expenses and no income,
it'll be tough even if you have some money saved up.
Thank you.
Please have a seat.
Why do you want to meet here?
Is it inconvenient for you?
Are you afraid Ms. Peem will be angry?
Ms. Peem and I have broken up.
Was it because of me?
Let's order some food.
Have you told your family we've broken up?
Not yet.
I don't know how to start.
My family wants us to get married.
I haven't been able to get in touch with you much lately.
Have you been busy?
A little.
Hello.
Uh, a table for two, please. Can we sit at our usual spot?
Your usual spot is taken, sir.
Would you mind sitting near your usual spot instead?
Uh, that's fine.
Then please come this way.
Please.
That's your table.
Okay.
Ms. Peem.
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
Here's your menu.
Thanks.
Anything you'd like to eat, Ms. Peem?
It's your regular place. I can eat anything.
Okay.
Would you like to move to another table?
It's alright.
Then let's do as we discussed.
I'll set a date for you to meet my family.
Speaking as someone in the same field.
There are certain types of women you shouldn't bring into your home.
Doing so could cause trouble to your livelihood.
You shouldn't introduce them to your family.
Please take this as a warning given out of concern.
You can just see me off here.
Let’s have a meal together again sometime.
Sure.
I'll get going.
Okay.
Ms. Peem.
Don't touch me.
Are you and him...
We're together.
Who I date is my own business.
You went official with Techin too.
Does he still pay you every time you get in his bed?
I'm happy for you
that you've found someone good.
You seem to be really compatible.
It's normal for people of the same level to be compatible.
Mr. David is much better than you.
I wouldn't feel the least bit embarrassed to be seen with him.
It still baffles me
how Techin dares to take a whore home and introduce her to his family.
I shouldn't have walked up to you.
Wait.
Don't tell anyone about us.
I'm ashamed of it.
Okay.
Hey.
I missed you so much.
Lately,
my family has been keeping a close eye on me.
Why?
Do they want you to get married?
Yeah.
And they're wondering
if I like men.
But it's good that your family likes that girl.
It helps clear that up a little.
I want to hold your hand
and walk outside without being afraid of anyone too.
Whenever you're ready,
I'll be happy to do it with you.
Then you wipe it for me.
If I pay today, I can do it now.
Ms. Peem.
Didn't she tell you I'm gay?
Please get out.
Get out!
♪ Even though my heart says I love you ♪
♪ Why am I like this? ♪
♪ I don't understand ♪
♪ What's wrong with my mouth and my heart? ♪
♪ Why won't they say the same thing? ♪